

# JOHN CHRISTOPHER PESQUERA

JUNIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### SUMMARY

With nearly two years of experience as a Junior Software Engineer, I have significantly enhanced my critical thinking skills and ability to write clean, efficient code for both front-end and back-end development. I have also collaborated effectively with other teams to deliver solutions aligned with client requirements.



## WORK EXPERIENCE

# SEBI Technologies Inc.

August 2023 - Present

Junior Software Engineer

#### School Management System

- · Able to work with a large amount of data and use it in development accordingly.
- Able to work with QA's and fix issues depending on their assessments.
- Able to investigate bugs and issues happening within the application and resolve them when necessary.
- · Able to achieve client requirements.
- Enhanced skills by creating dynamic and reusable code which can be used by other developers.

## SEBI Technologies Inc.

February 2023 - May 2023

Junior Software Engineer Intern

## Payroll System

- Developed lookup modules that are necessary for the system.
- Able to migrate old systems to a new one utilizing VueJS and Laravel.
- · Able to work collaboratively with other interns and employees.
- · Have training that are necessary for the given task.

## **EDUCATION**

# **Technological Institute of the Philippines**

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Graduated with distinction

#### **Parang High School**

2018-2019

2019-2023

Secondary Education

Graduated with Honors



# SEMINARS ATTENDED

- Project Management Tool Training using JIRA Software Webinar (2021)
- Artificial Intelligence from A-Z: Fundamentals of Data Science and Beyond (2022)
- Intelligent and Professional Interaction (2022)

# CONTACT

- +63 976 179 6876
- gmail.com
- Parang Marikina City
- https://xceedgone.github.i o/jcp-portfolio/

# SKILLS

- Collaboration
- Communication
- Critical Thinking
- **Decision Making**
- Work Flexibility

# TECH SKILLS

- Html and CSS
- GraphQL
- VueJS Framework REST API
  - **PostgreSQL**
- Php Laravel

# REFERENCE

#### **Francis Fernandez**

Junior Software Engineer

Phone: 0995 700 0896

# **Lawrence Caraig**

Junior Software Engineer

Phone: 0967 405 9432

